It's really sad you know, wedding ceremonies which should be a highlight of the day, if
not the highlight of a wedding day, have just become something that we almost joke about,
we can't wait till they're finished, we can't wait till it's over so we can start having
a good time.
After the wedding ceremony it should be that you can't wait to talk about how good it was,
how relevant it was, how real it was, how authentic and how much fun it was.
Hi I'm Ethan.
I'm Grace and we're currently on our honeymoon in the Italian Dolomites.
We actually decided to go with Jake when we saw him on another couple's wedding
video, coincidentally. We didn't really do much research. The way he just held
himself and the way he spoke, when we heard him we were like, "That's the guy
for us." Yeah, so we just booked him in right away, no hesitation, and we're so
glad we did because he was just an awesome celebrant. Everyone came up to
us afterwards saying what a great job he did and how much fun they had in the
ceremony which is exactly what we were after. So if you're if you're thinking
about booking Jake I'd say go for it you won't regret it.
Yeah 100% recommend. Good luck!
Wedding ceremonies have gone south I think largely because a) waffle.
Too much talk that isn't relevant to that couple getting married on that day.
Too much talk of things that could have been said at the last week's wedding or
next week's wedding. Every word at your wedding should be relevant to you, to
and personalities to your relationship.
The other thing that I think brings ceremonies down
is the cringe factor or awkwardness.
People talk about this all the time.
I think it often comes from people trying too hard
to get a laugh using punchlines, using wedding jokes.
It has such a high rate of just not landing.
But if we talk about things that are playful,
things that are observations about your journey,
you as a couple, things that have happened in your journey,
They don't have to be ha ha funny, knock it out of the park,
but there is no way people won't be smiling,
chuckling, grinning, or outright laughing.
They all achieve the same thing.
Serotonin release, people are happy,
and people are engaged in this ceremony.
And the last thing I think is that
they just feel not authentic.
They don't feel true.
It feels like someone is speaking
who doesn't really wanna be there,
who isn't invested in the couple.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is such a privilege
for me to be here today.
No, it's not.
You don't need to read that bit.
They should be able to tell that your celebrant cares
so much about you and the two of you
becoming a married couple.
They should be able to tell that there's been
a whole lot of prep done so that on the day,
the celebrant can not just be standing there reading,
but leading the atmosphere,
making your ceremony one that people will never forget.
And the other thing is momentum.
We want to make sure that even if we're talking
about the right stuff, if we talk about it for too long,
people are going to start looking at the view,
listening to the birds.
We want this ceremony to have momentum,
so we're building up to the whole crescendo
of the wedding day, which is the vows,
the promises that make you a married couple.
Everything in the lead up to the vows
is building up to that moment,
and everything after them is celebrating that they happen.
If you follow these rules, you'll have an incredible wedding.
My name's Jake. I'm a marriage celebrant based in Australia,
and I would love to help celebrate the two of you becoming married.
Thanks for listening. God bless.
Hi Jake! Just wanted to say thank you so much for all the help that
you've given us to have the best ceremony ever.
We're Molly and Julian and two months ago today, we got married by Jake.
We had Jake as our celebrant and our MC, and we can't thank him enough.
We had such a good day and he helped the day run so smoothly.
So thank you.
- We couldn't have found a better celebrant
and we highly recommend him for your special day.
- Thanks Jake. - Thanks Jake.
- He was amazing.
He kept me calm the whole day.
Everything just ran so smooth.
- We really love the personal and professional approach
taken by Jake and his team.
- Yeah, we honestly couldn't recommend Jake enough.
- Five stars Jake.
Thank you so much for everything you did for us.
- Thank you so much.
- Cheers.